http://www.advicediva.com/ad/privacypolicy.asp

Privacy Policy
Introduction
AdviceDiva.Com, owned and operated by Advice through Experience,
respects each individual’s right to personal privacy.
We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement.
This statement applies solely to information collected at AdviceDiva.Com and HowToForgetYourEx.Com (a domain which points to AdviceDiva.Com). For the purposes within this letter, the name AdviceDiva.Com will include the domain HowToForgetYourEx.Com.
Information Collection
AdviceDiva.Com collects information through our Web site at several points.
We collect the following information about primary visitors:
Email through our opt in contact form via ConstantContact.Com listed on all pages throughout AdviceDiva.Com.
Email and mailing addresses when an order is placed at AdviceDiva.Com
We may also collect emails which our users divulge about other people in the form of referrals.
Our monthly emailers have the ability to allow the user to forward the email to another recipient.
AdviceDiva.Com catches the email address.
Certain pages on AdviceDiva.Com allow the user to forward the url to another recipient via ConstantContact.Com.
AdviceDiva.Com does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information.
We collect the following general data that is not personally identifiable information:
Poll information from users in a monthly poll.
We do not collect demographic data.
We collect this information through orders placed at AdviceDiva.Com, orders placed through our affiliate program, Clickbank.Com, and through the available opt in box on all pages of our website provided by ConstantContact.Com. The information is collected voluntarily.
To receive our products and services, an email given is mandatory because many of our orders are digital products which are fulfilled via email delivery.
Email contact is also needed to ensure the consumer receives his or her product.
An address is required for all mailed products.
Other information we request is optional.
We do employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user’s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable AdviceDiva.Com to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users.
Our cookies do not have an expiration date. Our cookies
collect personally identifiable information based on the computer alone for our forums.
The Cookies enable to user to log in successfully to their account and use the forums.
No other information is collected from these cookies.
Third parties
AdivceDiva.com may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns gathered during thousands of customer visits to our Web sites each month but does not contain behavioral or identifying information about any individual member. We may also provide log files and other databases of user information to third parties for analysis, so we can get a better understanding of traffic through our site and thus improve our content offerings. AdviceDiva.com uses a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our sites. This company may use information about your visits to our and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Visual-Studio-Reviews.com's cookies.
Also be aware that we may buy and sell business assets and/or divisions; customer information is generally part of such a sale.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Other third-party vendors or ad networks may also be used to serve ads on this site.
Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, this site has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.
Banner advertising appearing on our Web site will not collect any information.
We allow no third parties to collect any information at our Web site.
Information Usage.
The information collected by AdviceDiva.Com will be used for order delivery and email distribution..
Users who provide information will receive a monthly emailer and any products they might have ordered.
Registered users will receive additional announcements from us about products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.
The information we collect will not be used to create customer profiles based on browsing or purchasing history.
We will not supplement information collected at our Web site with data from other sources.
We will not share data with any third parties.
We offer links to other Web sites.
Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies.
Their standards may differ from ours.
Our Web site offers public forums.
Please be advised that information posted in these venues becomes public knowledge.
If our policy on information collection or uses changes, will advise you by email.
Access to Information
AdviceDiva.Com maintains the accuracy of our information by customer and visitor entry only. Users may access their own personal information and contact us about inaccuracies they may find using our contact page.
Users may delete their information from our database by opting out of the emailers using the opt out button located at the bottom of each email and by visiting our forum and canceling their free membership.
Problem Resolution
If problems arise, users may contact AdviceDiva.Com by visiting our contact page. We are committed to resolving disputes within 48 hours.
Data Storage and Security
AdviceDiva.Com protects user information by employing ConstantContact.Com.
All emails are kept on their servers.
For customers, all credit card information is kept with Paypal.Com, Google.Com or PaymentOnline.Com, whichever payment processor the customer chose to use.
AdviceDiva.Com does not retain any credit card information on our servers.
